<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Simplicity</title>
    <description>Simplicity is a simple Window Manager that is heavily inspired by the Awesome window manager. I liked the idea but wanted something just slightly different.
</description>
    <link>http://durandj.github.io/simplicity/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://durandj.github.io/simplicity/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2014 18:44:38 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2014 18:44:38 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Logging Debug</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been working on getting logging added since that will definitely help with tracking down issues and makeing sure all goes as it should. Since I’m already using Boost I decided to go with Boost.Log. It took a bit of work to get setup since I’m still new to using the AutoConf toolchain with Boost and I’m a bit rusty with C++ but in the end I got it. It does some really basic logging. My next goal is to make logging a bit easier to use since I’ll be more inclined to log things if I don’t have to jump through hoops to do it. Currently logging looks something like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;#include &amp;lt;boost/log/core.hpp&amp;gt;

#include &quot;main.h&quot;

void log_something(void)
{
	BOOST_LOG_SEV(get_global_logger(), boost::log::trivial::debug) &amp;lt;&amp;lt; &quot;Yay!&quot;;
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I ommitted a bit more code but that’s the general idea. That’s not very friendly. I want to make this a bit easier to do so I’m going to add some helper functions so that you can just do this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;log_debug() &amp;lt;&amp;lt; &quot;Yay!&quot;;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s what I’m looking at for now. I would like to make things even better but I need to do some testing first and I want to keep my one step at a time approach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also need to do some work on the blog. I want to theme it at some point and it really needs some tools to make generating posts a bit easier. I’ll do some work on that when I need a break.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2014 13:37:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://durandj.github.io/simplicity/update/2014/10/20/logging-debug.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://durandj.github.io/simplicity/update/2014/10/20/logging-debug.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Initial Commit</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The basic goal for this project is two fold. One is to write some C/C++ code. I almost never get to write any C style code anymore. I’m almost always writing in Python, Perl, Java, and Javascript. These langauges are great and all but I first really learned to program in C and C++. This is a good opportunity to write some real C code! :) The other goal is to write THE window manager that I just love. I’ve tried a fair few different options already and while some are pretty great I just like the idea of having the one that was literally made for me. I’ve never done anything like this so it’ll definitely be a big challenge and there’s a lot for me to learn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My plan for development is to do things in little steps. I’m hoping that I can do frequent mini updates to keep things going and to prevent myself from getting stuck doing a really big project and find its got a fatal flaw at the very end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I spent a bunch of time already working on the basic build system. I decided to go with the AutoConf toolchain. AutoConf wasn’t the most pleasant to get setup but that’s done. Now I’m actually writing some code!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 04:12:53 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://durandj.github.io/simplicity/jekyll/update/2014/10/17/initial-commit.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://durandj.github.io/simplicity/jekyll/update/2014/10/17/initial-commit.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
