<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Simplicity</title>
    <description>Simplicity is a simple Window Manager that is heavily inspired by the Awesome window manager. I liked the idea but wanted something just slightly different.
</description>
    <link>http://durandj.github.io/simplicity//</link>
    <atom:link href="http://durandj.github.io/simplicity//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 12:36:12 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 12:36:12 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Initial Commit</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The basic goal for this project is two fold. One is to write some C/C++ code. I almost never get to write any C style code anymore. I’m almost always writing in Python, Perl, Java, and Javascript. These langauges are great and all but I first really learned to program in C and C++. This is a good opportunity to write some real C code! :) The other goal is to write THE window manager that I just love. I’ve tried a fair few different options already and while some are pretty great I just like the idea of having the one that was literally made for me. I’ve never done anything like this so it’ll definitely be a big challenge and there’s a lot for me to learn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My plan for development is to do things in little steps. I’m hoping that I can do frequent mini updates to keep things going and to prevent myself from getting stuck doing a really big project and find its got a fatal flaw at the very end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I spent a bunch of time already working on the basic build system. I decided to go with the AutoConf toolchain. AutoConf wasn’t the most pleasant to get setup but that’s done. Now I’m actually writing some code!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 04:12:53 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://durandj.github.io/simplicity//jekyll/update/2014/10/17/initial-commit.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://durandj.github.io/simplicity//jekyll/update/2014/10/17/initial-commit.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
